Minchan.
ミンチャン
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
You're popular, right?
モテるでしょ?
not at all.
全然
Really?
本当は?
Aren't you popular?
モテないの?
How about here?
どう、ここ?
You've come to a beautiful place.
綺麗な場所来たね
Do you always come on dates?
いつもデートで来いと来ないの?
Oh, it's not coming at all.
え、全然来ない
Aren't you coming?
来ないの?
That's right.
そうなんだ
Where are you going on that date?
どこだ、そのデートするときは?
movie.
映画
I like movies.
映 画 好きなんだ
What movie do you like?
何の映画が好きなんだ?
I love Hollywood.
ハリウォッド好きなんだ
It's cute.
可愛いね
I like it too.
俺も好きだよ
I also saw the novel.
小説も見たけど
Then you like me better.
じゃあ俺の方が好きじゃん
You too.
お 前も
No, me too.
いや、私も
Aren't you afraid of being expensive?
高いっておこわくない?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
I like Minchan's style.
ミ ンチャンスタイルいいね
How tall are you?
身長何本?
It's 160.
160なんだ
Min-chan is so shy.
ミ ンチャン恥ずかしがりやん
a little bit.
ちょっと
I'm shy.
恥ずかしがりやん
Looks good in a stylish place.
おしゃれなとこ似合うね
yes?
そう?
Minchan seems smart.
ミンチャンって頭良さそうだよね
Isn't it good?
良くないの?
That's right.
そうなんだ
I guess you can do math.
数学とかできそうじゃん
Let's go.
行きまーす
What about English?
英語は?
English.
英 語
You can do it.
できるんだ
Can't you speak?
喋れんの?
How much?
どんくらい?
Just a greeting.
挨拶くらい
I can do it too.
俺もできるよ
halo.
ハロー
What is your favorite hobby?
一番の趣味は何ですか?
Do you like manga?
漫画好きなの?
What do you like?
何好きなの?
手術改正
That's interesting.
面白いね
It's interesting.
面 白 いね
What about One Piece?
ワンピースは?
I just gave up on it.
普 通でやめちゃった
Why stop?
なんでやめるの?
Shall we go somewhere else soon?
そろそろ他のところ行ってみる?
Hello.
こんにちは
She's so beautiful.
めっちゃ美人だね
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いぞ
TRUE?
本当?
I wish I had become an idol.
アイドルやればよかったのに
I guess I'll do it.
やろうかな
Shall we do it now?
今からやる?
There's still time.
まだ間に合う
Because I'm 19 years old.
19歳だから
Great style too.
すごいスタイルもいいね
Are you doing any exercise?
何か運動とかしてるの?
No, nothing.
いや、何も
I haven't done anything lately.
最近 全然してない
I don't even go to the gym.
ジムとかも行ってないんだよ
She has a very naughty body.
すごいエッチな体しとる
Where do you usually go on dates?
デートいつもどこ行くの?
movie theatre.
映画館
Like a cafe.
カ フェとか
Do you like sweets?
甘いもの好きなの?
A cafe?
カフェか
What do you like?
何が好きなの?
My favorite food is yakitori.
好きな食べ物は、 焼き鳥
It's yakitori.
焼き鳥なんだ
I like yakitori.
焼き鳥いいね
It's not grilled meat.
焼き肉じゃないんだ
Your skin is pure white.
肌真っ白だね
Why?
何で?
It would be good if a lot came out.
いっぱい出ればいいでしょ
A lot of men will come.
男いっぱい寄ってくるよ
Isn't it necessary?
必要ない?
need.
必要
There are very few people with experience.
経験人数少ないでしょ
There's only two of us.
2人だけなんだ
That's right.
そうなんだ
It looks like there are two of us.
2人って顔してるもんね
Please show me your cute face.
可愛い顔ちょっと見せてごらん
Please remove it slowly.
ゆっくり外してごらん
You look at me now and think I'm cute, right?
今 見て私可愛いって思うでしょ?
I don't think so.
思わない
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いよね
Who do you say you look like?
誰に似てるって言われる?
Like Mitsuki Takahata.
高畑みつきとか
It might be a little similar.
ちょっと似てるかも
It's said sometimes.
たまに言われる
Your skin is so shiny.
肌がつやつやだよね
Really beautiful.
ほんと綺麗
pure white.
真っ白
It's like snow.
雪みたい
Because I don't dislike it.
嫌気しないので
What kind of sex have you ever had?
今までどんなエッチしたことある?
Have you ever had sex in the perverted place?
一番変態な場所でエッチしたことある?
It was in the car.
車の中だったんだ
How was the sex in the car?
車の中のエッチはどうだった?
Excited.
興奮する
Are you a little more excited than normal?
普通よりもちょっと興奮する?
That's right.
そうなんだ
Stand up.
立ってさ
Please show me your beautiful style.
綺麗なスタイル見せてください
It's super stylish.
スゲースタイリーわ
Aren't your breasts big?
おっぱいでかくない?
E cup.
Eカップ
Is there an E cup too?
Eカップもあるの?
Amazing, from the side.
すごいよ、横から
There is a bulge.
膨らみがある
Look behind you.
後ろ見て
Your butt is so erotic.
お尻がエロいね
You have a plump butt.
プリプリのお尻してるね
It is said.
言われる
Are you told?
言われる?
Only two people have ever done it.
2人しかやったことない
too good to waste.
もったいない
I'll be the third one today.
今日で3人目になっちゃうけどね
It's the third person.
3人目だ
Look behind you again.
もう一回後ろ見て
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
Try flipping up the skirt.
スカートめくってみて
It's big, your butt.
大きいね、お尻
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
I want to pen pen.
ペンペンしたいよ
Erotic and down.
エロい、そして下に
This is so see-through.
スケスケじゃん、これ
Butt.
お尻
Well, look here again.
じゃあこっち見てもう一回
Kuro-chan.
クロちゃん
This cute uniform, please.
このかわいい制服ちょっと お願いします
get nervous?
緊張する?
a bit.
少し
I'm so excited.
ドキドキだね
You're such a great oppa.
すっごいオッパいける
Looks like a celebrity.
芸能人みたい
Amazing boobs.
すごいオッパい
My oppa is big.
オッパ大きいな
Such pure white oppai.
こんな真っ白なオッパい
That's amazing.
すごい わ
I'm so excited.
テンションあっちゃうわ
Kuro-chan, then the skirt.
クロちゃんじゃあスカート
Min-chan has become worse.
みんちゃん下になっちゃったね
Even though my stomach is constricted.
お腹くびれてるのにさ
Your butt has such volume.
お尻こんなボリュームあって
Even though her face is amazingly biogenic.
顔がすごい生素系なのに
Such a disgusting body too.
こんな嫌らしい体も
Turn around.
後ろ回って
Too erotic.
エロすぎ
Look behind you again.
もう 一回後ろ見て
Beautiful butt.
綺麗なお尻
Min-chan, let me stick that in your ass.
みんちゃんそれお尻くぎ込ませて
pants.
パンツ
Show me that.
それ見せてごらん
It's 100 points.
100点です
Let me sink into you even more.
もっともっとくぎ込ませてよ
Pull it up.
上に引っ張ってよ
Have you ever seen a pose like this?
こんなポーズ見したことある?
That's an erotic butt.
エロい尻だな
Well, take a look here.
そんまいこっち見てみ
Well, Kuro-chan.
じゃあクロちゃん
These beautiful breasts.
この綺麗なオッパイを
Let's take a look.
ちょっと 見ちゃおう
I agree.
そうだね
Look at those nice tits.
いいオッパイ見ちゃって
soft?
柔らかい?
It's so soft.
すっごい柔らかい
Look here.
こっち見てみ
It's so beautiful.
めちゃめちゃ綺麗
Super beautiful breasts.
超綺麗なオッパイ
Makes me want to lick it.
舐めたくなりますね
That's making me tingle.
それな、チクビツンズンしてる
How does it feel to be touched?
チクビ触られるとどういう気持ちになるの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Beautiful tits.
綺麗なオッパイ
Well, Kuro-chan, come here next time.
じゃあクロちゃん、今度ここ
This is it.
これだこれ
Shall I wash my pants too?
パンツも流しちゃおうか
Just stand there.
そのまま立ってて
Your hair is growing properly.
ちゃんとお毛毛生やしてるんだね
Yeah, I'm fixing it.
うん、整えてる
Are you arranging it?
整えてるんだ?
The striped manga is erotic.
すじまんがエロい
Take a photo very close up.
めっちゃ近くで撮る
Come sit there.
そこ座ってこい
I even did some gymnastics.
体操するまでして
Do your best.
思いっきりやりとこい
Has it decreased?
減っちゃった?
It hasn't been shown yet.
まだ映してない
amazing.
すごい
Your pussy is so small.
マンコちっちゃいね
That's right.
そうなんだ
It closes with a bang.
ピシって閉じてるし
It feels like a 19 year old's pussy.
19歳のマンコって感じだな
Slowly spread it out with your own hands.
ゆっくりさ、自分の手で広げてみ
Yes, let's expand it.
そう、広げてみしておこう
earlier
もっと前
Come to that, there is a limit.
に 来て、そこがギリギリある
That's open.
そこが開いて
Let's open it up ourselves.
自分で思いっきり開いておこう
Pro-chan, please open this up more.
プ ロちゃん、これもっと開いてあげて
Rin-chan.
リンちゃん
Yeah.
うん
I'm filming everything from the inside of her pussy.
マンコの奥まで全部撮ってるよ
It's kind of bad.
なんか悪みや
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
this.
これ
Hey.
ねえ
But it's so beautiful.
でもすんげえ綺麗だよ
Look at the chestnut's face yourself.
くりの顔は自分で向いてみてよ
Yes, let me show you.
そう、見せておこう
This way.
こっち
What do you usually do?
いつも何する?
sometimes.
たまに
I do it sometimes.
たまにしちゃうんだ
When do you do it?
どういう時にするの?
Like when I read a naughty manga.
なんかエッチな漫画読んだ時とか
Do you read naughty manga?
エッチな漫画読むんだ?
sometimes.
たまに
Isn't it a video?
動画じゃないの?
Is it a manga?
漫画なの?
Mostly manga?
ほとんど漫画?
Yeah.
うん
It's kind of weird to watch manga.
漫画見るなんてなんか変態だね
He looks like a perverted high school boy, right?
変態な男子高校生みたいでしょ?
I guess so.
そうかな
That's right.
そうだよ
How many times do you say that?
それ何回も言っちゃうの?
Do it to you.
お前にして
Yeah.
うん
How many times are you going to do it?
何回かやるんだ?
About twice.
2回ぐらい
Will you do it twice?
2回やるの?
Are you as naughty as your face?
顔に合わせてエッチなの?
Well then, let's move on to four floors.
じゃあ今度4つん階になって
Stick your butt out as hard as you can.
お尻を思いっきり突き出してごらん
That's a sexy ass.
エロいケツだね
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Over here.
こっちで
Show me your butt.
お尻見せな
Please open your legs more.
もっと足開いてごらん
Hold both butts.
お尻両方持って
Do your best to open your asshole.
頑張って開いてお尻の穴
Let me show you.
見せてごらん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
Her butt is also very beautiful.
お尻もめっちゃ綺麗
Wasn't he the most perverted person in my life?
人生で一番変態な方でしたんじゃない?
I guess so.
そうかな
Amazing ass.
すごいお尻
You have such a cute face, but are you looking at that naughty butt?
こんな顔可愛いのにそんなエッチなお尻を見てんの?
Will you be hated?
恨まれちゃう?
other girl.
他の女の子
Then sit here.
じゃあ次にここに座って
Put your shoulders down and sit down.
肩足こみ落として、座ってごらん
Put your foot down.
足こみ落として
front.
正面
Raise only your shoulders and legs.
肩足だけ上げて
I thought and lay down.
思って横かかって
Diagonally.
斜めに
Open it there.
そこで開いてごらん
By yourself.
自分で
You have to open everything.
全部開かなきゃダメだよ
oh yeah.
そうそう
Have you ever seen a pussy this close?
こんな近くでマンコ見られたことある?
do not have.
ない
Where are you always?
いつもどこいじんの?
Mainly
おも
Do you use it?
ちゃ 使うの?
Don't use toys.
おもちゃは使わない
Do you do it by hand?
手でやるの?
That way?
そうやって?
My fingers are moving on their own.
指勝手に動いちゃってんじゃん
I like free gin.
フリージンの好きなんだ
Can't you go inside?
中に入れないの?
What if it's me?
自分だと何?
I can't go in.
入れないんだ
Well, I'll put in as much as I can today.
じゃあ今日いっぱい入れるね
Even though she's so cute, I'm getting excited as a pervert.
こんな可愛いのに変態のテンション上がっちゃうわ
Okay, then stand up.
よし、じゃあ立ってごらん
Lou-chan.
ル ー ちゃん
Those cute lips.
この可愛い唇
Even if you inject it.
注射しても
I want to.
したい
Shall we do it?
やっちゃおうか
cute.
可愛い
It suits baseball.
野球に合うね
She looks so naughty though.
こんなエッチな姿だけど
Now, like this.
今ね、こんな
Lou-chan.
ルーちゃん
Inject your cute face.
可愛い顔に注射を
go
いく
Yo.
よ
Can I wait a little longer?
も っとしていい?
Lu-chan, please take out your tongue.
ルーちゃん、ベロ出してみて
Lu-chan, lick that.
ルーちゃん、それ舐めて
Next, Kuro-chan, stick out your tongue.
次に黒ちゃん、ベロ出して
Would you like to try this?
これ舐めてみる?
Please lick it more like tongue.
もっとベロのようにいっぱい舐めてごらん
Make sure to lick your lips too.
唇も全部舐めてごらん
Finally, put your tongue in Kuro-chan's mouth even more.
最後もっと黒ちゃんの口に舌いっぱい入れてごらん
Black-chan, suck it.
黒ちゃん、吸ってあげて
Look this way.
こっち向いてよ
It's suitable for me.
こっち向きな
Please put a lot of tongue in it.
いっぱいベロ入れてごら
yeah.
ん
So, what do Kuro-chan and Rin-chan taste like?
で、 黒ちゃん、リンちゃんの味は?
cute.
かわいい
Highest?
最高?
Highest.
最高
Rin-chan, please raise your arm.
リンちゃん、腕あげてみて
Can you give it to me?
あげてみ?
Have you ever been licked here?
ここ舐められたことある?
Isn't there?
ないの?
It's my first experience.
初体験だね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Kuro-chan, lick it all.
黒ちゃん、全部舐めて
I want to lick all the sweat.
汗全部舐めたい
Tell me how it feels.
どんな感じか教えて
Suck it.
吸ったり
Did you taste the sweat?
汗の味した?
Yeah.
うん
I'll clean everything.
全部きれいにしちゃうんですよ
You're getting beaten up really bad.
すんごい殴られてるね
Hey.
ねえ
I'm sweating all the time.
一調して汗かいてる
Gently lick it at first.
優しく最初ペロペロね
Lick me gently.
優しく舐めて
full of shapes.
いっぱいの形
Please show me your hair being licked.
舐められてる髪を見せてください
Rin-chan, your nipples are erect.
リ ン ちゃん、乳首立ってるよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
It rolls down from the bottom.
すごい下から転がる
Fill it up.
いっぱいにしてね
Her waist has a naughty shape.
腰なんかエッチな形になってんじゃん
You're exhausted.
くたくたしてるじゃん
Try leaning against the wall.
それ壁に寄っかかってみてよ
glass.
ガラス
Go this way.
こっち行って
Step on it.
足乗って
Open it.
開いて
I can go further back.
もっと後ろ行けるよ
Lick it a lot and make it feel good.
いっぱい舐めて気持ちよくして
Rin-chan is seriously cute.
リンちゃんマジで可愛いよ
So now it's time to take turns.
じゃあ今度は交代
Can you lick a man's penis?
男の人のチクビ舐めれる?
can?
できる?
Come down further and lick it.
もっと下出してペロペロって舐めて
Lick it like that.
そうまま舐めて
too
も
Just suck it and suck it.
っと チクビにチューチューして吸ってごらん
Now, Rin-chan, turn to me.
じゃあリンちゃんこっち向いて
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Chikubi, try sucking more.
チクビもっと吸ってみ
Put it on once.
口一回つけて
Look here at the end.
最後こっち見てごらん
Has your tingle gotten hard?
チクビ固くなった?
Well then, Rin-chan, just sit there.
じゃあリンちゃん、そのままさそこ座ってごらん
What is this?
これ何これ?
penis.
おちんちん
penis?
おちんちん?
Looking at the camera again.
もう一回カメラ見ながら
what?
何ですか?
penis.
おちんちん
Penis?
お ちんちん?
Try taking off your pants.
パンツ脱がしてみて
It's getting a little bigger.
ちょっと大きくなってるね
Take a closer look.
近くで見てごらん
Very close.
めっちゃ近くで
What do you think of this?
どうですかこれは?
Don't touch it yet.
触っちゃダメまだ
What are you trying to touch?
何触ろうとしてんの?
It's early, isn't it?
早いでしょ
Look carefully.
見てよちゃんと
delicious?
おいしい?
big?
大きい?
Can it be bigger?
もっとでっかくできる?
Take a look.
先っぽつんづんしてごらん
hand
手
in.
で
Try holding it.
握 ってごらん
copper?
どう?
The life of the third person?
3人目のちのち?
Do you like it a lot?
結構好き?
This is Kuro-chan, guess your cute face.
これ黒ちゃん、可愛い顔当てて
Tip.
先っぽ
Have you ever had this done?
これやられたことある?
Penis on the face.
顔にちんちん
do not have?
ない?
Well, Kuro-chan, I'll ask you to guess everything.
じゃあ黒ちゃん、全部当ててあげてもらう
I'm doing something wrong.
悪いことしてるんだけど
Also on the lips.
唇の上も
This cheek too.
こっちのほっぺも
It looks like a cat.
猫ちゃんみたいだね
Then, get your feet together.
じゃあべろ足
My feet are sticky.
べってべろ足
Try throwing the tip a little.
先っぽちょっと投げてみて
Try throwing them all.
全部投げてみて
Chin chin.
ちんちん
From the root.
根元から
Berobero.
べ ろべろって
Slender legs.
べろ足
This is my hand.
こっち手じゃん
by chance
たまたま
Put it in your mouth.
口 に入れてごらん
Maru more.
丸もっと
Have you ever entered it?
入れたことある?
In your mouth.
口に
Isn't there?
ないの?
Put them all in.
全部入れてごらん
It's so naughty.
めっちゃエッチだよ
En-chan.
えんちゃん
Throw more and more from the bottom to the tip.
その下から先っぽまでべろもっと投げて
Then raise your mouth.
じゃあ口あげて
I drank it and ate it.
あくって食べちゃって
Give it a lot and make it feel good.
いっぱい投げて気持ちよくしてあげて
While facing this way.
こっち向きながら
Throw your dick while looking at the camera.
カメラ見きながらちんちん投げて
delicious?
おいしい?
Don't you know?
わかんない?
Then, make more noise and suck as much as you can.
そしたら、もっと音立てていっぱい吸ってごらん
Squeeze yourself.
自分をしごって
oh yeah.
そうそう
Please put up a lot of sex etc.
エッチなどいっぱい立ててごらん
Kuro-chan, open your legs.
黒ちゃん足開いて
More dull.
もっと歯濁しく
Give it all you've got.
そのべろ思いっきり出して
Lick the entire tip.
先っぽ全部舐めて
Everything on the table.
表のほうも全部
Cali too.
カリも
Clean everything up.
全部きれいにしてあげて
While facing this way.
こっち向きながら
It's so beautiful.
すんごいきれいだよ
Try making it more sloppy.
もっと歯濁しくしてごらん
Use your hands too.
手も使って
While facing this way.
こっち向きながら
Suck louder.
もっと音立てて吸って
Buzzing.
ブチブチって
Go all the way to the bottom.
一番奥までいってごらん
Ching Chin.
チンチン
To the deepest part.
一番奥まで
There?
そこ?
That's it?
そこだもん?
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
I'll go in more.
もっと入るよ
Come on.
カモン
Impossible?
無理?
Move it well.
よく動かしてあげて
Because you talk a lot.
い っぱい喋らすから
There's a lot of dick in your mouth.
口の中チンチンっていっぱいだね
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
Look at the camera.
カメラ向いてごらん
Keep facing me.
ずっと向いてごらん
It was really big.
すんごい大きかったね
Try making it more sloppy.
もっと歯濁しくしてごらん
It has grown so big.
こんな大きくなっちゃった
Just wet it with saliva.
ツバでいっぱいさっき濡らしてごらん
Get it all wet.
いっぱい濡らして
Hold it in your hand.
さきっぽ手で持って
Yes, it's better to use your hands.
そう、手でいじめたほうがいい
Take a good look at it.
ちゃんとチンチン見てごらん
Lick it again.
もう一回舐める
Hold your head here.
こっち頭持って
Try moving it.
動かしてごらん
You don't have to go all the way inside,
あんま奥までいれなくていいから、
quickly.
早く
Terin-chan, look this way.
てりんちゃん、こっち向いて
Make a face like you're licking me.
舐めてる顔にしてごらん
Try licking it again.
もう一回舐めてごらん
Please pull back as hard as you can.
い っぱ い引ってごらん
最後
Try licking it once again first.
もう一回たまたまから先に舐めてごらん
Take a quick look.
パクッとしてごらん
I've gone so long now.
すんごい行っちゃった今
Come on Javed.
ジャベットおいで
Yakkuro-chan.
やっくろーちゃん
Shall we tease Rin-chan in bed?
ベッドでりんちゃんいじめようか
Shall we do that?
そうしようか
Would you like Rin-chan to sleep?
りんちゃん寝てもらうか
river
かわ
good.
いい
Look over here.
こ っち向いてよ
Don't be shy.
恥ずかしがるなよ
cute.
かわいい
Erotic.
エロ
That's a great body.
素晴らしい体だね
I want to feel good.
気持ちよくしたいな
So beautiful.
すっごいきれい
Feel good.
気持ちよく
People who lick boobs are so cute
い っぱい舐める人がめちゃめちゃかわいいよ
this.
これ
It's on the other side.
反 対側だよ
It's really crunchy.
すんごいコリコリしてるよ
Can you figure it out yourself?
自分でわかる?
It's so beautiful.
す んごいきれい
Kuma-chan, please come down.
くまちゃんどうも下行ってごらん
Open your legs.
足開いてごらん
Try opening it again.
もう一回開いてみして
Don't hide your face.
顔隠さないで
Look here.
こっち見て
cute.
かわいい
Please open it again.
もう一回開いてごらん
It's kind of tight.
なんか締めてるね
Pro-chan, open it up as much as you can.
プロちゃん、思いっきり開いてごらん
Amazing pussy.
すっごいよろいまんこ
Rino-chan liked chestnuts.
りのちゃん、栗が好きだったよ
Lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐めて
Show me everything.
全部見せて
Please clean up all the chestnuts.
栗いっぱい片付けてごらん
Pro-chan, put the whole bottom in the hole.
プロちゃん、穴に下全部入れて
bean paste
あ ん
Come in here and enjoy.
こ に入ってまくるべ
Hold your legs.
足持ってごらん
Take it to yourself.
自分に持ってごらん
Pro-chan, lick everything from my asshole.
プロちゃん、お尻の穴から全部舐めて
Up to the top.
上まで
Lick it from my asshole.
お尻の穴からいっぱい舐めて
Do you want to lick it?
舐めたい?
full.
いっぱい
Pro-chan, lick it again.
プロちゃん、もう一回舐めて
Please put the red bean paste in there.
あ んこ入れてごらん
Kuri-chan, lick me again.
栗ちゃん、もう一回舐めて
Look here.
こっち見てごらん
Make it a face.
顔にして
Kuri-chan, is it delicious?
栗ちゃん、美味しい?
Finally, look, lick it all.
最後、ほら、全部舐めてごらん
Butt and all.
お尻も全部
Kuri-chan, look.
栗ちゃん、ほら
Please open the red bean paste you licked.
舐めたあんこ開いてみしてください
Hold it yourself like this.
自分でこうやって持って
Sister, have you ever used a phone?
姉ちゃん、電話使ったことある?
There isn't.
ないよ
So, can I use this?
じゃあ、これ使っていい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
Don't just say it.
勝手に言っちゃダメだよ
It's hard.
かまんだよ
can.
できる
Not today.
今日じゃなくてね
Let's watch Papping Cho.
パッピングチョー見ようかな
When you go, go.
行くとき、行くって
I'll go again today.
もう一回行くよ、今日
I'm gone.
行っちゃったの
It's red.
赤 じゃん
I tried it once myself, and it was my first time.
自分で一回やってみて、初めて
Try the challenge.
チャレンジしてみな
Let's talk.
話しちゃうね
Are you feeling it?
感じてる?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Another one
もう一
Can you go twice?
回 行ける?
I can go again.
もう一回行けるよね
Let's look at it again.
もう一回見してみよう
can?
できる?
I don't know.
わかんない
Try it.
やってみて
Let's look at it again.
もう一回見してみよう
I can't do it again.
もう 一回いけない
Have you ever used this?
これ使ったことある?
naughty items.
エッチなアイテム
Also the Chin Chin type.
チンチン型も
You've never used it, right?
使ったことないでしょ
Big vibe.
大きいバイブ
It's this big.
こんなでかいの
Do you want to compare it with the face?
顔と比べてみる?
It's bigger than your face.
顔よりでっかいよ
Will this fit?
これ入る?
Won't you come in?
入んない?
Really?
本当に?
Shall we try it?
やってみようか
Looks like it'll fit in.
入りそう
This also works as a phone.
これも電話として
Do it when you enter.
入るときにして
Look at my face.
顔を見てて
It's kind of harsh.
なんかきついね
Do you know what's in the big one?
大きいの入ってるのわかる?
that's right.
そうです
Can I move around here too?
ここでもまんこの辺、ぐるぐるしていい?
Can I do the spinning thing?
ぐるぐるするやつやっていい?
sorry.
ごめん
I'll do it.
やっちゃう
Look.
ほら
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
Is it like this?
こういう感じ?
Are you busy?
こっさざってる?
Small.
ちっちゃい
Swing it on.
振り乗せて
My nose hurt.
鼻いちった
To the back.
奥まで
Because Rin-chan is getting tired.
りんちゃんがつんどいになってるから
Push your butt out all at once.
お 尻をもう一気にお尻につき出して
Put it in your ass all at once.
もう一気にお尻に入れよ
Wow, that's amazing, put something on your butt.
すごいすごい、なんか尻につけて
It fits great.
すごい入る
Rin-chan, Shin-chan come in and show your face.
りんちゃん、しんちゃん入って顔見せて
Can you tell if you go in there?
そこで入ったらわかる?
It's tough.
きついね
Move it a little more.
もう少し動かして
Look over here, sideways.
こっち見てくれ、横に
Rin-chan, look here.
りんちゃんこっち見て
It's really sticky.
すっごいしみつけてる
amazing.
すごい
Try touching the chestnut.
くり触ってみて
Rin-chan then looked up again.
りんちゃんそしたらもう一回上向き
I'll put this in again.
もう一回これ入れるよ
Look.
ほら
I'll put it in again.
もう一回入れるよ
amazing.
すごい
Don't paint your dog, Rin-chan.
わんこ塗るねえじゃん、りんちゃん
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
It's fun to go.
行きとくの楽しい
Come with me because it feels good.
気持ちいいから一緒に
Let's go.
行くぞ
I'll go again
また行っちゃ
Did you?
った の?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't your dog turning bright red?
わんこ真っ赤になっちゃったんじゃない?
I went there many times.
何回も行った
I got a nose because I put a wife in it.
ワイブ入れたから鼻いっちゃった
Rin-chan.
りんちゃん
refer to.
指
I put it in because it definitely felt good.
絶対気持ちいいから入れた
I need to adjust my feet.
足調整ないと
Touch the top that feels good.
上の気持ちいいとこ触って
Does this feel good?
これ気持ちいいの?
So please keep spelling it out.
じゃあつづるつづけてごらん
My strength is broken.
力割れに
Don't go on your own.
勝手に行くなよ
Rin
りん
chan, chestnut itself.
ちゃん、 くり自体
It's two fingers.
指2本ですよ
Touch the top that feels good.
上の気持ちいいとこ触って
Open your fingers inside.
中で指開いて
Enter the comfortable part above.
上 の気持ちいいとこ入って
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
this.
これ
Try shaking it yourself with your fingers.
指 で自分で振りいじってごらん
Try touching it.
触ってみて
You always use your fingers, right?
いつも指でおなにしてるでしょ?
So go and try it.
それで行ってみして
Look, I'll do it myself.
ほら、自分でやる
This is erotic.
エロいね、これ
The dog is so full, isn't it?
わんこぱんぱんになってんじゃん、
I can play it.
吹けるって
Don't make me feel good.
気持ちよくしないで
It's okay to say it out loud.
大きい声でいいね
I went there once.
1回もいっちゃったね
Well then, this Kubo-chan.
じゃあ、このくぼちゃん
Next is Rin-chan.
次は、りんちゃん
First, try holding it in your hand.
最初、手で握ってごらん
Touch it slowly.
ゆっくり触って
Shinchin, cover yourself.
しんちん、かたぶして
Look closer to my face.
顔、近づけてごらん
Yes, you, nipples.
そう、お前、乳首
Chin, chin, chin with the nipple.
乳首でチン、チン、チン
Yes, grab a lot.
そう、いっぱい握ってごらん
Try rubbing it with your nipples.
乳首でこすってごらん
Rin-chan, her nipples are so big.
り んちゃん、乳首、ビンビンじゃん
Don't feel good about binging.
ビンビンで気持ちよくしないで
Has it become hard?
かたくなった?
Ching, ching, ching.
チン、チン、チン
Take out your tongue.
ベロ出して
Stroke all cylinders.
気筒全部撫でて
All the front ones too.
前のほうも全部で
I just let it out.
今、ベロベロ出した
Tease the tip a lot.
先っぽいっぱいいじめて
oh yeah.
そう、そう
I'll eat it all.
全部食べちゃう
I tried smoking it more, and it was very chewy.
もっと吸ってみ、ちごちごあって
Please eat hard.
一生懸命食べてください
Shinchin, have a drink, don't make yourself feel good.
しんちん、一杯、気持ちよくしないでごらん
Please give me plenty of sun.
すんのげっちりあげてごらん
I kept looking at the camera.
ずっとカメラ見たもん
Chigochigo, hurry up.
ちごちご、早くして
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I think this one is good too.
こっちもいいと
I saw it, quickly.
見たもん、早く
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Sorry about that.
それ、すみません
Try squeezing it quickly with your hands.
手で早くしこしこしてみ
Put on your spit.
ツバつけて
Try spitting on it.
ツバ垂らしてごらん
Then squeeze it.
それでしこってみ
In the brim.
ツ バで
So have it.
それで持って
tip
先っぽ
stomach.
い
Hold it closer.
も っと近くで持って
Make me feel so good that I can't stand it.
我慢できないくらい気持ちよくしてごらんよ
Get it sooner.
もっと早く持って
amazing.
すごい
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Be white.
身を白いで
The one from Six.
シックスのやつ
Six's one.
シ ックスのやつ
Please put it in my pussy from there.
そこからマンコ入れてもらえな
Suck it a lot.
いっぱいしゃぶりついて
Come on, just the two of us.
ほら、二人で
At least it feels good.
気持ちいいとくせめあって
Also include Pro-chan.
プロちゃんも入れて
Okay, let's bring Rin-chan in here too.
じゃ、りんちゃんも入れよ、こっち
Put it in Rin-chan's pussy.
りんちゃんのマンコ入れよ
If you have your own Chin Chin, please put it in.
自分でチンチン持っていたら入れてごらん
Just in case it won't come.
一応こないって
No.
違うよ
Have you ever moved?
動いたことある?
that.
それ
Move your front face like this.
前顔こうやって動いて
Rub your pussy all over my cock.
チンチンにマンコをいっぱいこすりつけてごらん
Make yourself feel good.
気持ちよくしてごらん
You can also make an M shape on top of that.
そこの上でもM字できる
Become a crab crotch.
ガニ股になって
If you can stand your feet.
足立てれば
yes.
そう
So try moving.
それで動いてみて
Pro-chan, follow me from below.
プ ロちゃん、下からちょっとついてね
Pro-chan, go for it.
プロちゃん、ギャンって
Look below.
下見てごらん
You can come in.
入ってもいいよ
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Look at it as if it's full of dick.
チンチン入ってる感じでごらん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Let's make you ugly deep inside yourself.
自分の奥までブスさせてごらん
Look.
見て
Pro-chan, turn around once and then go the other way.
プロちゃん、一回向いて逆
That's right, try tightening it.
そう、締めんじゃ手ついてごらん
Pro-chan, please follow me slowly from below.
プロちゃん、下からゆっくりついてごらん
Take it slow.
ゆっくりね
Lift your hips.
腰を浮かしてごらん
Is it possible?
できそう?
Please come along one more time.
もっと一回ついてごらん
Try lifting your hips more.
もっと腰を浮かしてごらん
Pull it out, please.
抜いてよ、つんばいで
Wash it.
おしれろ
Pro-chan, look this way.
プ ロ ちゃん、こっち向いて
Face the camera.
カメラ向いて
Please put it in.
チンチン入れてごらん
You look naughty.
ヘッチな顔してるよ
Rin-chan, look this way.
リンちゃん、こっち向いてごらん
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
Face the camera.
カ メラ向いて
It's better to show your face.
顔見せたほうがいい
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
Follow me there.
そこでついてごらん
Pro-chan, please follow me more.
プロちゃん、もっとついてよ
Turn sideways.
横向いて
Pro-chan, please fill it up.
プロちゃん、いっぱい入れてごらん
Pro, put it in.
プ ロちゃん、入れて
Please stab me as hard as you can.
い っぱい刺してごらん
It really stings.
すごい刺さってるよ
It's really perverted.
ほんと変態だね
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Let's do it again, naughty play.
またやろうね、エッチな遊び
Thank you for today.
ありがとうね、今日ね